<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-11-30T19:32:25.060" Score="18" ViewCount="220" Body="&lt;p&gt;We have had a lot of sites throughout the history of Stack Exchange that have suffered problems dealing with &quot;recommendation&quot; questions. That is, questions which are intending to gather a collection of recommended items, from which the author selects their preferred answer out of. Here, this would be questions like the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I enjoyed &lt;em&gt;Lucky Number Slevin&lt;/em&gt;, what movies out there are like it that I'd enjoy?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Are there any good Steampunk movies out there?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, these kinds of questions have very poor performance on the sites. This is because their functionality conflicts with the intent of our sites. Our goal is to have expert solutions that are identified by the depth of the knowledge of our users. The accepted answer system is founded on the principle that an answer serves as an &lt;em&gt;understood closure&lt;/em&gt; to the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The issues of itemized lists are elaborated in various places: &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;blog articles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://gaming.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/997/handling-game-recommendations-how-can-we-solve-these-two-problems-of-quality&quot;&gt;essays&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://gaming.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/1617/so-what-actually-is-a-game-rec/1841#1841&quot;&gt;quick notes&lt;/a&gt;. To summarize it concisely: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;They require extensive maintenance (which never happens for long) to be accurate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The voting on such lists conflicts with the scope of voting on the site (people vote as if it was a poll, not based on quality)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No single item in the list can &lt;em&gt;conclude&lt;/em&gt; the question, which conflicts with the nature of Q&amp;amp;A.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Many problems result in trying to reduce their scope, due to the subjectivity of how &quot;narrow&quot; criteria can be. So if any are allowed, generally all are allowed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Compounding on that, the ease and spread of itemized list recommendations gives a very poor image of the site as it does not showcase the expertise that many are looking for.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, at the moment, there isn't necessarily an intent to invite or allow recommendation questions. Recommendations were in fact noted as off-topic during the definition phase, and there's no trace of them in the top voted on-topic questions. Nevertheless, I'm writing this to hopefully get people in the mindset to understand why recommendations are hazardous, and consequently help setup a &quot;no-rec&quot; policy on the site &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; it opens to public beta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:32:36.147" LastActivityDate="2017-06-22T20:20:14.417" Title="Dealing with &quot;recommendation&quot; questions" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="404" CreationDate="2011-11-30T19:52:16.010" Score="25" ViewCount="525" Body="&lt;p&gt;We already have two questions with an obvious SciFi/Movies overlap (that have already been asked on &lt;a href=&quot;https://scifi.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;SciFi.SE&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/7/22&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/7/22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/5/22&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/5/22&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do we want to handle this overlapping area?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.587" LastActivityDate="2014-04-23T09:12:27.697" Title="SciFi/Movies overlap" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="8" CommentCount="6" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-11-30T19:55:04.777" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's going to happen...  They are still valid questions for the domain of this site, not something that would be migrated, and thus should be allowed to have their own life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T19:55:04.777" CommentCount="4" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0"  Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;"  />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-11-30T20:00:40.360" Score="8" Body="&lt;h2&gt;My opinion:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the question is indeed an exact duplicate (as in the two examples provided above), defer to the one that was asked first (in these cases, SciFi), and close the duplicate (in these cases, Movies).  This seems to be the rule across other SO sites.  Closing in this case is the same as closing a duplicate, and is in no way saying the question is off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the question is about the &lt;em&gt;making&lt;/em&gt; of the movie, it probably belongs on Movies (although there are many SciFi questions about the making of movies, so refer to #1 above).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the question is about the &lt;em&gt;story&lt;/em&gt; of the movie (&lt;em&gt;Explain the end of Inception&lt;/em&gt;), either site is fair game; refer to #1 above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the question is about some especially scientific-ish aspect, ask on SciFi (&lt;em&gt;How do light sabers work?&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2020-06-04T15:14:02.303" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T20:00:40.360" CommentCount="8" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-11-30T20:04:19.190" Score="5" ViewCount="54" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are already three of them:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/10/41&quot;&gt;Did the FBI know about the mole in the police department and did they interfere with the investigation?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/5/41&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/5/41&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/6/41&quot;&gt;What does the ending of The Tree of Life mean?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm sure more are going to come, and they don't strike me as directed towards experts. What should our policy on them be?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="41" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.220" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T01:15:04.970" Title="Are questions about specific plot details on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2011-11-30T20:18:16.513" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/3698/movies/3702#3702&quot;&gt;top-voted example question during the definition phase&lt;/a&gt;, yes, questions about plot details are on topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T20:18:16.513" CommentCount="5" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2011-11-30T20:26:15.713" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;What would be the point of a movie QnA if you can't ask questions about the plot of a movie?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="52" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T20:26:15.713" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2011-11-30T20:44:08.330" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some references:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Literature, we have a temporary policy allowing recommendations, found &lt;a href=&quot;https://literature.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/203/policy-trial-notice-book-recommendations&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  This has had some mixed results, but without enough traffic to get a definitive answer we've left it open for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Role Playing Games also allows recommendation &lt;a href=&quot;https://rpg.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/system-recommendation&quot;&gt;questions&lt;/a&gt;, here's their &lt;a href=&quot;https://rpg.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/1070/are-game-recommendation-questions-disallowed-on-rpg-se/1071#1071&quot;&gt;meta discussion&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="52" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:45:51.767" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T20:44:08.330" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="13" CreationDate="2011-11-30T20:47:26.093" Score="14" ViewCount="126" Body="&lt;p&gt;Already I am seeing tags used for individual movies - Inception, Tree-of-life, Star Wars.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should we be encouraging tagging on individual movies, or will that get out of hand with each movie getting its own tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can see the argument for series of movies - Star Wars, James Bond - but I am unsure about the use of tags for individual movies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T21:55:28.420" Title="Should tags for individual movies be encouraged" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9" CreationDate="2011-11-30T21:03:36.313" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think that you take it on a case by case basis with the good rule of thumb being it's OK to tag series of movies.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can see Inception being a good tag because it is a movie that generates a lot of discussions, but would we really want a Snakes on a Plane tag?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T21:03:36.313" CommentCount="4" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9" CreationDate="2011-11-30T21:07:55.570" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can't find where I've read about this before, but I'm quite sure that little-used tags are automatically removed by the system after some time.  So to some extent, this will be a self-correcting problem.  Tags for movies of low popularity will, after a time, not clutter our tag collection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T21:07:55.570" CommentCount="7" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-11-30T21:47:47.817" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Doesn't this pretty much preclude questions about scifi movies being asked on Movies.SE because almost (if not every) question about a scifi movie is by its very nature Science Fiction?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is Star Wars a movie?  Yes - let me post it on Movies.SE.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Oh wait, it's also scifi related... maybe I should post it on SciFi.SE instead?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The average person isn't going to agonize over the decision; they're going to post it on the &quot;wrong&quot; site and have with a lousy user experience when they find out their question has been moved/closed or that there's a battle going on over whether or not they posted it in the right place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ditto for Literature.SE / SciFi.SE.  Questions about SciFi books are appropriate for both places.  What about Superuser + AskUbuntu/Apple.SE?  Pretty much anything in AskUbuntu is appropriate for Superuser as well as any Mac questions under Apple.SE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IT Security / ServerFault?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Statistical Analysis / Mathematics?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Theoretical Physics / Physics?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Major potential for overlap has been created as StackExchange has been expanding and it's only going to get worse.  If questions are appropriate for multiple sites, then their asking needs to be facilitated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;My Solution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why not create some kind of association between overlapping sites where the &quot;Questions with similar titles&quot; that appear when the title for a question is entered can be expanded to search other sites that will overlap?  This way, if anyone tries to ask a question on SciFi.SE that may already exist on Movies.SE or Literature.SE, they'll appear in the results and hopefully prevent the duplicate from being asked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; They should appear in general search results too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58" LastEditorUserId="58" LastEditDate="2011-12-01T02:31:07.130" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T02:31:07.130" CommentCount="6" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9" CreationDate="2011-11-30T21:47:48.763" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;The basic thing to think about, is how you want to use tagging on your site. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://gaming.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Gaming&lt;/a&gt; intends to tag any game's title. Yes, it will eventually result in odd tags like &lt;strong&gt;[atom-zombie-smasher]&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;[fish-squid-time-machine]&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;[the-great-gatsby]&lt;/strong&gt;, but for us, the game's title is the &lt;em&gt;core&lt;/em&gt; thing that people sift through information on. It does cause problems if a game doesn't get enough questions (it needs 2 within 6 months), or if the title is long (let's not get into the 26 letter titles), but we work to handle those issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scifi.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;SciFi and Fantasy&lt;/a&gt;, on the other hand, does &lt;a href=&quot;https://scifi.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/412/general-tagging-practices&quot;&gt;a variety of things&lt;/a&gt;. As appropriate, the tags go for author, series, universe, or work, resulting in the individual names only for isolated cases. This allows them to focus on more prominent elements than being narrow, as the narrowness isn't as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As such, it is &lt;em&gt;viable&lt;/em&gt; to tag every title if that is decided on, but it is by no means necessary. The site may be able to operate with a less granular tagging system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T16:38:20.340" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T21:55:28.420" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2011-11-30T22:54:19.703" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think although there will always be ambiguity now and again, the major distinction should be made as to the community of expert each SE caters to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Movies.SE is more about the making of the movie: casting, effects, production, script, scenes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;SciFi.SE is more about the universes of Fantasy and Science Fiction: the lore, the reasons behind how or why things are how they are, i.e. the nerdy stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, and especially when the movie comes from a book, the plot/storyline and characters will be the real major overlap, and then it's on-topic of both sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="57" LastActivityDate="2011-11-30T22:54:19.703" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-11-30T23:20:36.590" Score="22" ViewCount="407" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Possible Duplicate:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/220/final-tv-decision&quot;&gt;Final TV Decision&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's the whole thing with &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/2026/tv-buffs&quot;&gt;TV Buffs&lt;/a&gt;, they're still pretty far off from getting a beta, I'd say.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So do we take an active stand to encourage questions about TV, so that the proposal to merge the two gains more ground, or do we avoid treading on our couch slouching friends' toes? (no offense meant to home theater goers)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And then between 'hell yeah' and 'not at all' we have gray areas: what of high-production series (e.g. frigging game of awesome thrones?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="57" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:49:37.243" LastActivityDate="2011-12-30T00:40:21.697" Title="Should we cover TV Series here?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="0" ClosedDate="2012-01-18T02:31:31.807" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-11-30T23:54:14.150" Score="28" ViewCount="588" Body="&lt;p&gt;There's going to be lots of posts that ruin endings, how to deal with them? Should spoilers be included in the question title?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;spoiler&quot;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt; What to spoiler text?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastEditorUserId="1190" LastEditDate="2019-12-10T08:01:15.920" LastActivityDate="2019-12-10T08:01:15.920" Title="What's the policy on spoilers?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;faq&gt;&lt;policy&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 4.0" />
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-11-30T23:59:37.593" Score="2" ViewCount="54" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are several movies that share the same title. Sometimes they are completely different movies and not remakes. How should we tag these?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/foo-1950&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;foo-1950&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;foo-1950&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/foo-2010&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;foo-2010&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;foo-2010&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, the series title may be the name of an individual movie. For instance, &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/starwars&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;starwars&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;starwars&lt;/a&gt; could refer to episode 4, or the entire series. What to do here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T01:45:43.163" Title="Tags for movies with the same name and remakes?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="18" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2011-12-01T00:12:03.517" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it is reasonable to mimic SciFi's &lt;a href=&quot;https://scifi.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/1/is-it-important-to-mark-spoiler-questions-as-such&quot;&gt;lead&lt;/a&gt;, which is essentially to use the Spoiler markup as you have demonstrated in your question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They seem to also have &lt;a href=&quot;https://scifi.meta.stackexchange.com/a/453/2912&quot;&gt;blacklisted&lt;/a&gt; the &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/spoiler&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;spoiler&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;spoiler&lt;/a&gt; tag, which seems to make sense to me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would add to that &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/a/89582/165502&quot;&gt;this discussion&lt;/a&gt; about over/mis-use of the spoiler tag. In short:  Don't make your entire question a spoiler.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-20T10:29:51.513" LastActivityDate="2015-10-16T11:37:08.897" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="19" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="21" CreationDate="2011-12-01T00:17:09.393" Score="7" ViewCount="116" Body="&lt;p&gt;My question &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/33/66&quot;&gt;&quot;What is done in post-production?&quot;&lt;/a&gt; got criticized for not showing any reasearch effort or being general reference. Although it may be valid, I can't find a reference to such a rule and I can't remember ever encounter this on other SE-sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I think if these questions should be ruled out, then the FAQ should state this clearly and we should be clear about which questions qualify for this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.587" LastActivityDate="2014-04-23T09:12:27.697" Title="Should we outrule questions without research effort?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19" CreationDate="2011-12-01T00:23:23.760" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Hover over the 'down vote' arrow for any question, and you will see this text:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;This question does not show any research effort; it is unclear or not useful&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For further reading, see these questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/q/97880/165502&quot;&gt;Is lack of (other) research a reason to downvote?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/q/102811/165502&quot;&gt;Should a clear lack of research be grounds for closing a question?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-20T10:29:51.513" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T00:23:23.760" CommentCount="5" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19" CreationDate="2011-12-01T00:41:23.410" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;Please see &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/02/are-some-questions-too-simple/&quot;&gt;Are Some Questions Too Simple?&lt;/a&gt;, in the blog post the following chart was brought up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/aEcq5.png&quot; alt=&quot;Is it to simple?&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As seen above for your question we will close it as general reference (i.e. not a real question).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also I don't have an image to back it up, but before you ask a question in this site you were presented with a page and it had something along the lines of &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Don't ask too simple questions. We want to build this site with well researched information (questions and answers)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe someone has a reference for this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T00:41:23.410" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="22" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2011-12-01T01:15:04.970" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Like others I don't see the point in not being able to discuss plot points here.  Is it more that you have concerns about questions about interpretation.  If so, I have some sympathy with your concern, interpretation questions are unfortunately rather open ended for a QnA forum, but I still think it is fair game to ask them here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You say that they are not questions to 'experts' - but someone may have watched Inception 20 times and read about it, who can provide more enlightened commentary about it than someone who has only just watched it once.  For instance the Inception question raises the point about Cobb's Totem before he inherited his wife's - something that I had not considered before.  The question is phrased in a very open manner rather than specifying some specific area of interpretation - but I don't overall the forum is better served with them than without.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T01:15:04.970" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="17" CreationDate="2011-12-01T01:45:43.163" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am still unconvinced that individual movies should be tagged at all, but have been led to believe that little used tags will eventually disappear automatically - so I guess this doesn't matter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, to answer your question, the easy part is the year.  I would propose following your 'year' convention, which seems pretty simple for example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ladykillers-1955&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;ladykillers-1955&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ladykillers-1955&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ladykillers-2004&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;ladykillers-2004&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ladykillers-2004&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the question about series, perhaps encourage a series suffix:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/jamesbond-series&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;jamesbond-series&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;jamesbond-series&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/starwars-series&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;starwars-series&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;starwars-series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T01:45:43.163" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="28" CreationDate="2011-12-01T02:38:12.517" Score="13" ViewCount="112" Body="&lt;p&gt;Can I ask questions about Bollywood (Indian) movies, in private beta? Or is it inappropriate as private beta has few users?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="87" LastActivityDate="2013-01-07T09:27:15.753" Title="Asking questions about Bollywood movies" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="29" CreationDate="2011-12-01T02:53:02.693" Score="4" ViewCount="60" Body="&lt;p&gt;I wanted to ask this question in Movies Private Beta, but when I Post my question, it gives an error saying,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Oops! Your question couldn't be submitted because:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;It does not meet our quality standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can someone explain why my question is rejected? (Sorry about my stupidity....)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the question I wanted to ask:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;'Blue Valentine' movie ending&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;At the end of the movie do they (Dean &amp;amp; Cindy) separate?  or Any other&#xA;  thoughts you got about the movie ending?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tags&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;ending&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="87" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T03:25:40.647" Title="Why this question does not meet quality standards" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26" CreationDate="2011-12-01T03:11:18.563" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;As long as the question is good, I think it is okay. I am pretty sure a few of us know some Bollywood movies as well. If not we can always invite an expert into private beta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T03:11:18.563" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="29" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="27" CreationDate="2011-12-01T03:25:40.647" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;The overall word (character) length is short so the filter must have picked up on that and other things that I am not aware of in the system of SE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What are you trying to determine, a certain outcome? Maybe phrase it as follows,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Title: Outcome of relationship at the end of 'Blue Valentine'&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Always put meat into the title.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Body:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I have not watched this movie so this a todo section for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Place in a little spoiler section to jog the memory of those who did see  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Explain your research for and against why you think the separation occurred (camera placements, character expressions .. etc)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T03:25:40.647" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-01T09:27:00.920" Score="6" ViewCount="63" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/faq&quot;&gt;main faq page&lt;/a&gt; is missing the &quot;What kind of questions can I ask here?&quot; section completly, and has wrong contents under &quot;What kind of questions should I not ask here?&quot; - copied from some programming site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is this being taken care of, before the site go live?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The quality standards here are pretty rough, so trying to add more text to satisfy them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;(Yes it worked, without above sentence I couldn't post this question)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="106" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.220" LastActivityDate="2016-07-13T11:07:20.353" Title="main faq page is not complete" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-01T11:06:11.467" Score="-2" ViewCount="187" Body="&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of 'spoiler' questions on this site. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Who kills this guy in this film?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;How many times does this happen in this film? etc etc.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The reason I joined this public beta is because, like many of you, I have a love for movies. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example question that I would love to ask:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Who are the cinematographers that you would regard as seminal, and why? and regarding this, what are some classic films that I should watch to see their work?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now this question would not be allowed, because it is subjective. However it seems like this would be a GREAT place to ask it. Where else is there such a well structured site with such a great and knowledgeable fan base?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So my question is, will these kinds of questions be allowed? Or is this just going to be a site dedicated to movie trivia?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'd love to be able to look at questions like this and see a big list of films to watch that people have talked about and decided on. A bit like this question: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tinyurl.com/so-cxxbooks&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.tinyurl.com/so-cxxbooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EDIT - I propose we allow kind of list question on the site. I for one would love to be able to look up a question which tells me what the best anime films to watch if I've never seen any before, or for music, or some quintessential noir films, zombie films, romantic films etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would also add that disallowing subjective answers on a site dedicated to an artform - which is inherently subjective, does not make sense. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The rule for non-subjective questions came from these sites being initially set up for technical topics (like stack overflow) where it is essential to provide factual, canonical answers. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="49" LastEditDate="2013-10-22T20:08:22.437" LastActivityDate="2013-10-22T20:08:22.437" Title="concerns about the rules of these sites conflicting with the goals of this particular one" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="22" FavoriteCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-01T11:21:22.393" Score="27" ViewCount="685" Body="&lt;p&gt;Are identify this movie questions to be encouraged?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They are one of my favourite tags on &lt;a href=&quot;https://gaming.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/identify-this-game&quot;&gt;gaming&lt;/a&gt;, but quite a few are closed due to lack of details or often multiple edits are needed to turn it into a proper question with enough details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="84" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:09:36.773" LastActivityDate="2016-07-13T12:23:53.657" Title="Identify This Movie Questions?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;&lt;identify&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="220" CreationDate="2011-12-01T11:24:07.753" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;The problem I see is if the site becomes popular (which is the goal), then you might be into the same situation as stackoverflow was and you end up needing to split it into multiple sites anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="84" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T11:24:07.753" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31" CreationDate="2011-12-01T11:43:58.893" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think those question are very interesting and get some great discussions. I would also like to ask people for recommendations, but at the end of the day this is a question and answer site and those answers are too subjective and are better suited to &lt;a href=&quot;http://chat.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;chat&lt;/a&gt; or a movie forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, you can't really accept an answer that is always true. Maybe you accept Fred's answer of 3 movies but then the next month I come back with a list that totally blows Fred's out of the water.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="84" LastEditorUserId="84" LastEditDate="2011-12-01T12:21:55.070" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T12:21:55.070" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="220" CreationDate="2011-12-01T12:18:44.507" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;There was a discussion on Area 51 regarding this: &lt;a href=&quot;https://area51.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/2817/why-not-merge-movies-and-television-and-give-both-a-chance&quot;&gt;Why not merge movies and television and give both a chance?&lt;/a&gt; The question received 32 upvotes and the answer suggesting they &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; merge received 26 upvotes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the question has now been tagged &lt;code&gt;status-declined&lt;/code&gt; so it appears the powers that be disagree. &lt;em&gt;It would be nice to get an explanation from the mods on the reasons for this!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So this leaves the question of where we draw the line between TV and Movies. There are many categories; here I'll list whether I think they should be here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Films that were originally given a cinema release - obviously fine here.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;TV series that never branched into cinema - definitely not here. (This would include series like Game of Thrones.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Films that have been released on DVD/video only - probably fine here, but there may be exceptions like Futurama, where the films came from a TV series and were later shown as TV episodes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;TV series that later had a movie - the movie itself is fine here, but there can be overlap again (e.g. &quot;in the Simpsons movie Homer did X, is that a reference to the TV series?&quot; would be acceptable here &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; a TV.SE site)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;TV movies or feature-length TV dramas - I don't know, but probably restricted to TV.SE.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After writing all this I really think the two proposals &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be merged. There is a lot of overlap, and many of the basic concepts like plot, characters and storytelling apply to both. Heck, there are plenty of one-off TV dramas that are longer than some cinema-released moves (e.g. Phone Booth is barely over an hour long IIRC).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="118" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-05-03T08:41:02.670" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T12:18:44.507" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30" CreationDate="2011-12-01T13:40:28.773" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Actually no it doesn't the community comes up with the FAQ so we are supposed to bring about the scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you see that banner at the top of this meta?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take ownership of your community - &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/the-7-essential-meta-questions-of-every-beta/&quot;&gt;Read The 7 Essential Meta Questions of Every Beta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yeah it's there for you to look at it and click.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first two questions there are:  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are questions about [subject] on or off topic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;What should our FAQ contain?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T13:40:28.773" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31" CreationDate="2011-12-01T13:42:45.700" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why are questions like these not &lt;em&gt;normally&lt;/em&gt; allowed?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because it's a pain to clean up when everyone had their fun with it. It's that simple really.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In that C++ question you linked, users are aggressively editing that question. You just don't notice it. Those 41 answers you see might actually be 41 visible answers and 50 deleted ones for all intents and purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently there is someone still cleaning up the &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/194812/list-of-freely-available-programming-books&quot;&gt;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/194812/list-of-freely-available-programming-books&lt;/a&gt; question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also that list is not all C++ books, it is the &lt;em&gt;definite&lt;/em&gt; C++ list. One in which the community agrees on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now another user somewhere else already complained about trivia. Since trivia is about basic foundation of movies here then maybe some too basic barrier should be employed to step up the non-trivial nature of questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think about it for a second. It's a Q&amp;amp;A site. You give a question. I give you an objective answer. This is not a discussion forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Who are the cinematographers that you would regard as seminal, and why? and regarding this, what are some classic films that I should watch to see their work?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this we can impart Programmers Six principles of subjective&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;inspire answers that explain “why” and “how”.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;tend to have long, not short, answers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;have a constructive, fair, and impartial tone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;invite sharing experiences over opinions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;insist that opinion be backed up with facts and references.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;are more than just mindless social fun.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For one your question is way too broad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Who are the cinematographers that you would regard as seminal&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A. We have moved in one direction here. With n different answers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;and why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We now have n different variations of each A. type answers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;and regarding this, what are some classic films that I should watch to see their work?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now we are up another layer to the type of answers that come in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there anything wrong with this? Not really sure, you may need to be checking Literature and Science Fiction sites instead of comparing it to StackOverflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You see, this is why we are in private beta so that we can experiment and broaden/tighten the scope to something we can all agree on. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Convince the community that these type of questions bring across constructive answers and then you got my vote at least.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do you do that? &lt;em&gt;Ask questions on the main site&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&quot;&gt;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&lt;/a&gt; for more info.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T12:35:01.887" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T13:42:45.700" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="38" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-01T13:46:55.370" Score="11" ViewCount="69" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am looking at this question, &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/71/&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/71/&lt;/a&gt;, and wondering if it's a good fit here. It feels more an economy subject.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="105" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.220" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T19:27:07.443" Title="Is the Blu-ray/DVD question on-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="39" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="38" CreationDate="2011-12-01T14:08:03.860" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would say that it is not on-topic.  It is a question of business-models, marketing strategy, product management, technology ... very little to do with the content of Movies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Technology does impact Movies - as resolutions go up and new technologies like 3D or all digital filming starts to impact the design of movies this is on-topic - but this cost of the disks is not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T14:08:03.860" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-01T14:27:27.363" Score="16" ViewCount="306" Body="&lt;p&gt;In order to prevent this site from turning into Trivia central we need some borders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't think we can get all in one go (or even at the end of private beta) but we could at least start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Working Draft&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Movies &amp;amp; TV - Stack Exchange&lt;/strong&gt; is for Movie &amp;amp; TV enthusiasts. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If your question generally covers &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Analysis of content or theme of all forms of Movies/TV&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Identifying a Movie or TV series&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Questions about a Movie/TV show's production.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;The works of a director / an actor / a writer related to Movies/TV&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Movies also includes &lt;strong&gt;Made-For-TV movies&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Direct-to-DVD&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Mini-Series&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that the following subjects are considered &lt;em&gt;off-topic&lt;/em&gt; here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Distribution&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Movie/TV purchasing/viewing locations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;The operation of playing a movie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Banal trivia that does not add to the understanding or appreciation of the title.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;TV news and current affairs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;A title's release date or rumors about a specific title or series.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Please note that &lt;strong&gt;spoilers are allowed here and may be out in the open.&lt;/strong&gt;  Read at your own risk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="40" LastEditDate="2012-02-06T14:43:31.957" LastActivityDate="2013-05-16T15:03:30.497" Title="What should our FAQ contain?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;faq&gt;&lt;7-essential&gt;" AnswerCount="7" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="4" CommunityOwnedDate="2011-12-08T15:03:25.453" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-12-01T15:59:02.727" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think we certainly have to allow those kind of questions. When we move out of beta, and the site will be open for everyone and not just the experts, it will be an important feature (ask the experts, if you can't find it out yourself). This is a Q &amp;amp; A site, and I don't see a reason why Identify This Movie Questions should be disallowed. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="36" LastEditorUserId="49" LastEditDate="2015-01-06T00:18:19.003" LastActivityDate="2015-01-06T00:18:19.003" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="38" CreationDate="2011-12-01T16:26:45.270" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I say it &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We seem to be (whether this is adviseable or not) preferring to create &lt;em&gt;format specific&lt;/em&gt; rather than &lt;em&gt;genre specific&lt;/em&gt; sites. (i.e: literature, movies, comic books, television).  Sci-fi is the outlier in that respect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my mind it makes no sense to tell someone it doesn't matter where they ask a question about a sci-fi movie's content, but that they definitely can't ask their question about the business of movies on Movies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="32" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T16:26:45.270" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="55" CreationDate="2011-12-01T16:30:12.923" Score="8" ViewCount="267" Body="&lt;p&gt;At least two users I have talked to said they are not interested in this site if it is just Trivia. To me trivia is well trivial,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Who is the main actor in Superman?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How many cars are in Gone in 60 seconds?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basically anything that can be answered within a few seconds on a Game Show. Am I wrong in thinking this or are most questions on this site trivia? Can someone define trivia and when does a question fall into and out of the definition? I rather for this not to be a trivia site so I have stopped asking questions until I am sure I am doing it right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2020-06-04T15:14:02.303" LastActivityDate="2011-12-09T00:32:04.590" Title="What's trivia and where do we draw the line?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="45" CreationDate="2011-12-01T16:50:35.273" Score="-2" ViewCount="87" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just hit the reputation cap, and I am not sure that's a good thing or not. Currently the privileges are relaxed. So I assume when public beta opens the privileges causing a gap in what we were once able to do for example close and re-open questions&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3000     Vote to close, reopen, or migrate any questions&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there any reason against relaxing reputation cap during private beta?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="68" LastEditDate="2011-12-05T21:09:41.550" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T21:09:41.550" Title="200 rep cap should be relaxed for Private Beta" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="45" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2011-12-01T17:08:23.673" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Non-technical reason:&lt;/strong&gt; I can't think of a good reason participants in the private beta need an edge in getting rep just on account of participating in the private beta.  All sites have to deal with the requirements being hiked up, it's just part of the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical reason:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;Your &lt;em&gt;official&lt;/em&gt; rep calculation can be viewed at any time:&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/reputation&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/reputation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suspect it would be a bit of a pain to maintain an exception for a short time period at the beginning of a site's life which would invariably become increasingly pointless as the site aged.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="32" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.220" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T17:08:23.673" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2011-12-01T18:01:45.437" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't think a relaxation of the rep-cap is really needed. At the start of a beta enough mods are looking over the site, so it's time, that users can build up reputation to gain rights. The relaxation on needed reputation to gain privilieges helps, that active participants gain privileges while the site is in beta. So in the midst of Beta the mods can start look over different sites. At the end of beta (including the open beta) enough users will have reached 10K or 20K.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T18:01:45.437" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="47" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-01T19:05:39.950" Score="5" ViewCount="139" Body="&lt;p&gt;Looking at this question, &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/99&quot;&gt;What is a &amp;quot;performance capture&amp;quot; animation movie?&lt;/a&gt;, I tried to vote to close it, but none of the reasons fit well. I would have liked to vote to close it due to being a &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/q/86043/&quot;&gt;general reference&lt;/a&gt; kinda question. Have a look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/02/are-some-questions-too-simple/&quot;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt; for background.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="105" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.943" LastActivityDate="2014-04-23T09:12:27.697" Title="Should we ask for a 'general reference' close reason?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;close-reasons&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31" CreationDate="2011-12-01T19:09:27.983" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;The question, as currently stated, is &lt;strong&gt;way&lt;/strong&gt; too broad, it's the same equivalent of asking who the most influential book authors are and what should I read to get a good sample of their work?  I could see this working, maybe, on literature if it was written “Who are the most influential sci-fi authors and what works highlight this influence?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="52" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T19:09:27.983" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2011-12-01T19:30:26.147" Score="-3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Probably we should be given an option to have a spoiler checkbox clicked and let the framework append a (SPOILER) in the question. Plus it is not wise to reveal the plot or give away the ending in the  Question. That should be made very sensitive as this forum is going to have a lot of movie watchers and googlers in future!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="131" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T19:30:26.147" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="51" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43" CreationDate="2011-12-01T19:45:06.827" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Your first question is a &quot;general reference&quot; question, easily answered with a visit to IMDB. Therefore, it would be a very bad question here, and not because it is &quot;trivia.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second question might be a good question, although it needs some clarifiction. Is it asking how many were stollen? Is it asking how many cars were used during the production? Is it asking how many cars were visible on screen?  In any case, I suspect any of those questions would fit on this site. I suspect they wouldn't get very many up-votes, though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T19:45:06.827" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40" CreationDate="2011-12-01T19:50:23.487" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;General Reference questions should be off-topic.  This includes questions that can be easily answered by a visit to IMDB or similar resources. Example off-topic questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Who starred in [X movie]?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What is [X movie] about?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What is the first movie that [X person] acted in/directed/produced/wrote?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And questions that can be easily answered by a simple Google or Wikipedia search:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What is [movie-making technology]?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is [X movie] based on a book?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-12-01T19:50:23.487" CommentCount="5" CommunityOwnedDate="2011-12-08T15:03:25.453" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="58" CreationDate="2011-12-01T23:38:42.340" Score="18" ViewCount="839" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is pointing out obvious plot holes really on topic?  This question has a lot of upvotes, but to me it seems like a candidate for a &quot;Yes, that was a plot hole.&quot; and a close vote.  Even on the original question on scifi the answer is very &lt;em&gt;discussiony&lt;/em&gt;.  Kind of interesting, but not terribly useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/61/in-back-to-the-future-why-dont-martys-parents-ever-mention-how-similar-he-loo&quot;&gt;Why don&amp;#39;t Marty&amp;#39;s parents ever mention how similar he looks to the Marty of 1955?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="32" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.587" LastActivityDate="2011-12-15T20:31:56.663" Title="Yes, that was a plot hole, and?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="220" CreationDate="2011-12-01T23:59:05.117" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;The proposal is marked [status-declined] simply because the site launched and the merge didn't happen. Now, as to whether it should (or shouldn't) happen&amp;hellip; I'll leave that to the experts here to chime in. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Closing that Area 51 discussion brings that discussion out of the theoretical (a &lt;em&gt;proposal&lt;/em&gt;) and into &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; forum, where the actual users charged with the responsibility of &lt;em&gt;building&lt;/em&gt; this site can discuss it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I would like to dispel two &lt;strong&gt;weak&lt;/strong&gt; reasons to consider a merger:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merge TV or it will never launch.&lt;/strong&gt; That's never a good reason in and of itself. Either they're a complementary audience, or they're not. Combining sites only to prop up the numbers is never done. The audiences have to complement each others' interests or you'll never get the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Network_effect&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;network effects&lt;/a&gt; you need to reach critical mass in the subject.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where will TV Theatrical Releases Go?&lt;/strong&gt; I'm not buying that one either. TV is just one source of story lines for movies. I'm sure you can discuss one in the context of the other without worrying too much about crossover. If they are that inseparable, this site will have to include comic books, plays, short stories, books, news events, history, poetry, and stand-up comedians, too.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastEditorUserId="69" LastEditDate="2011-12-02T03:42:57.900" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T03:42:57.900" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43" CreationDate="2011-12-02T00:20:41.267" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would simply add a line to your faq and &lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; overt trivia off topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Banal trivia that does not add to the understanding or appreciation of the movie is off topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simple enough. You &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; don't want this site to open up to a glut of &quot;I was just wondering...&quot; bar room talk. &quot;How many Storm Troopers died in the series?&quot;, &quot;List all the movies where the sequels surpassed the original&quot; &amp;hellip; blah, blah, blah. That's not good Q&amp;amp;A. It's a game show.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh... and, yeah; Simple reference questions like &lt;em&gt;&quot;who wrote [X]?&quot;&lt;/em&gt; are right out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T00:20:41.267" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="56" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2011-12-02T00:25:14.977" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;One of the purpose of the reputation cap is keeping a user from earning an &lt;em&gt;undue&lt;/em&gt; amount of reputation for a single, popular contribution. It's a throttling mechanism to keep a balance between on-going contribution and popularity. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If anything, &lt;strong&gt;the reputation cap is needed &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; during the private beta.&lt;/strong&gt; There are far fewer post and everyone is concentrating (and voting) on what little there is to vote on. So, certainly there is an &quot;undue&quot; (or at least a &lt;em&gt;disproportionate&lt;/em&gt;) amount of rep being doled out during the private beta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastEditorUserId="69" LastEditDate="2011-12-02T03:17:11.110" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T03:17:11.110" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="57" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="47" CreationDate="2011-12-02T00:58:35.307" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is my opinion and not any statement of official policy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The General Reference close reason has been implemented on a limited number of sites on an experimental basis. But I'm starting to feel that the adverse community effects are worse than the problem it was designed to solve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When someone asks &quot;Who was the author of [X]?&quot;, it should certainly be closed as uninteresting to answer (i.e. &lt;em&gt;general reference&lt;/em&gt;). So what they are presented with is this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;general reference&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  This question is too basic; it can be definitively and permanently answered by a single link to a standard internet reference source designed specifically to find that type of information. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;but &lt;strong&gt;the impression it sends to everyone watching&lt;/strong&gt; is &quot;Your question is already in Google. Go find it yourself.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In communities where the issue of &quot;General Reference&quot; has come up, they inevitably start enumerating which Internet resources will become purveyors of the verboten material&amp;hellip; rather than focusing on which questions will be interesting to the site. It all becomes very dismissive and new-user unfriendly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think it's better to explain in your faq if particular type of question is not appropriate for the site (even if it's just to say &quot;no general reference&quot;), and then simply close them as off-topic with a reference to the faq explaining why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &quot;General Reference&quot; close reason was my response to users who ask lazy questions without any effort, research, or context put into it. It satisfied that feeling you get when you just want to hit someone upside the head and say &quot;Why don't you just go flippin' look the thing up yourself!&quot; But in sober retrospect, I think it's better for community building if you educate users what it is to ask interesting questions rather than just slapping a 'dummy' sticker on it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastEditorUserId="69" LastEditDate="2011-12-05T03:54:55.900" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T03:54:55.900" CommentCount="5" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="58" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="53" CreationDate="2011-12-02T01:23:52.860" Score="16" Body="&lt;p&gt;This type of sophistry is just a rhetorical questions disguised as being clever. Close as &quot;not constructive.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nobody really wonders why The Terminator didn't casually walk up to Sarah Connor and break her neck instead of shooting up a bar. It doesn't add to the understanding or enjoyment of the movie. I really hope this site has a bigger vision and simply closes these questions down as &quot;not constructive.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T01:23:52.860" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="59" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="220" CreationDate="2011-12-02T15:00:29.843" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;I agree with @RobertCartaino 's dispelling of those two weak reasons, and I feel my own opinions on this matter are strong enough to warrant another answer and not a comment that could get lost in the shuffle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe that movies and television are two &lt;em&gt;fundamentally different things&lt;/em&gt;. Yes, they overlap in terms of storytelling technique at times (should we therefore allow &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; fiction in here?) and also personnel at times (in that case, should the discography of Will Smith, Jennifer Lopez or Lil' Bow Wow be on topic here?), and they both boil down to Moving Images With Sound Attached For Pleasure Effect (so by that logic, video games and music videos would also be covered as well). But honestly, movies and television are incredibly easy to differentiate 90% of the time. We should not bend this site's content just to make up for the 10% of content where there is debate. And also, the audiences for both are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the same. It's only recently, as cable television has started to up the quality of the artform, that television has even been acknowledged as an artistic equal to movies. &lt;strong&gt;Do we think that real movie professionals, the ones we want to use this site, would take us seriously if we have a &quot;Glee&quot; question next to one about &quot;There Will Be Blood&quot;?&lt;/strong&gt; I realize there's that big of a genre disparity within movies as well, but I think we run the risk of coming across as foolish by lumping television and movies together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't want this to sound like I don't want a TV stack exchange. My college major was television production. &lt;em&gt;I have a degree in television&lt;/em&gt;. I love television. I love television way more than movies. I would love to ask a million questions about &quot;Friday Night Lights&quot; &lt;em&gt;right now&lt;/em&gt;, but I don't want to do that on a site that also has movies. Because they are different things. It astounds me that it's taken movies this long to launch, but I feel that's indicative of the Stack Overflow audience, as that's who makes up the core group of users who get sites to private beta. A movies site is something we can pitch to the general public and get them to use. Then that audience can push a TV site through as well. &lt;strong&gt;The TV proposal isn't working because the audience isn't here yet, and I think this Movies site is going to help us get that audience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the scope of this site is already &lt;strong&gt;insanely broad&lt;/strong&gt;. Movies. All movies. All movies ever. That covers...a LOT. Why are we so anxious to just add potentially &lt;strong&gt;more noise to this site&lt;/strong&gt;? Going back to my &quot;Glee&quot;/&quot;There Will Be Blood&quot; example, do any of you really want to slog through questions about both movies AND TV shows you don't like/watch?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keep this site focused on movies and make it awesome. The TV crowd will come.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="126" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T15:00:29.843" CommentCount="7" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="61" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="220" CreationDate="2011-12-02T15:56:21.607" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would include all movies, even if they are split up in multiple parts. That would include mini-series like Wild Palms or shows like Game of Thrones, that have one story line. That would not include  Star Trek, where every episode is independent of the others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T15:56:21.607" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="62" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40" CreationDate="2011-12-02T17:12:13.170" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;A clear definition what is on-topic. We need some sentences on what is on-topic. 'Questions about movies' is far too cloudy. Which questions are good. As I see the questions so far, I think the following might match:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;questions about analysis of content or theme of movies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another type of question is in &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/32/identify-this-movie-questions&quot;&gt;discussion&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;questions about identifying a movie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are more questions asked currently, but I cannot catch them into a good sentence describing them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:49:37.243" LastActivityDate="2011-12-02T17:12:13.170" CommentCount="0" CommunityOwnedDate="2011-12-08T15:03:25.453" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="63" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="69" CreationDate="2011-12-02T18:36:45.487" Score="3" ViewCount="97" Body="&lt;p&gt;The question asks about &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/1/to-what-extent-were-the-central-characters-in-wedding-crashers-improvising&quot;&gt;To what extent were the actors in Wedding Crashers improvising?&lt;/a&gt;, to which a user replied with answer sourced from movie trivia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even the OP asks for other scenes, it is clear this is a case of it's in the trivia that's all there is to it. The only other over riding answer would be straight from the actor's mouth (or one of their interviews)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But to focus, by the votes, users have basically said this answer is useful. The fact that the answer comes from the trivia section is no fault of the user who answered though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So should these trivia style (extra features, little known facts from the DVD) questions be allowed?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.943" LastActivityDate="2011-12-03T04:33:08.223" Title="Is this question on Wedding Crashers trivia?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="65" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="67" CreationDate="2011-12-03T00:29:33.707" Score="0" ViewCount="63" Body="&lt;p&gt;Would a questions asking for suggestions for good online blogs or podcasts where movies are reviewed be on-topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are some questions like this on Stackoverflow, e.g. &lt;a href=&quot;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/1711/what-is-the-single-most-influential-book-every-programmer-should-read&quot;&gt;'single most influential book every programmer should read'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-05-23T12:35:01.887" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T16:59:45.820" Title="Questions about reviews and reviewers" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="10" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="66" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="63" CreationDate="2011-12-03T01:02:31.850" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why do you ask this question?  I'm guessing the reason is know if it ought to be closed as off-topic according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/a/55/22&quot;&gt;this answer&lt;/a&gt;.  But I don't think asking &amp;quot;Is X trivia?&amp;quot; is sufficient to decide if something is on or off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also don't think that making trivia automatically off-topic is useful.  And here's why...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What is trivia?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&quot;http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/trivia&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;dictionary.com&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;triv·i·a   [triv-ee-uh]&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;plural noun&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;matters or things that are very unimportant, inconsequential, or nonessential; trifles; trivialities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The very definition of &amp;quot;trivia&amp;quot; shows how completely subjective the term is. What is unimportant to you may be very important to me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Is this question trivia?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, it is. I've never seen the film, and have no interest in seeing it, so &lt;em&gt;everything about that film&lt;/em&gt; is, to me, &lt;em&gt;very unimportant, inconsequential, or nonessential&lt;/em&gt;.  However, to a person who enjoys that film, knowing how improvised it was may have great importance, and may enhance their enjoyment of the film.  There are many films I do like that have improvised portions, and knowing that makes it more enjoyable to me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Should this question be off-topic?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do not think this question should be closed as off-topic. But if we do choose to close it as off-topic, it needs to be for a better reason than &amp;quot;because it's trivia.&amp;quot; The vast majority of questions on this site are trivia to someone. In fact, one could say the entire topic of this site is trivia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And before our FAQ says &amp;quot;trivia is off topic,&amp;quot; I think we need a far more precise and objective definition of &amp;quot;trivia&amp;quot; than is provided by a standard dictionary. (In other words, I think we shouldn't make trivia, per se, off topic, but instead use some other objective standard to define which questions are &amp;quot;too simple&amp;quot;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2020-06-04T15:14:02.303" LastActivityDate="2011-12-03T01:02:31.850" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="67" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="65" CreationDate="2011-12-03T01:04:47.497" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Please read the text below that question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;This question exists because it has historical significance, but it is not considered a good, on-topic question for this site, so please do not use it as evidence that you can ask similar questions here. More info: FAQ.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think this means that asking &quot;Which reviewers should I read?&quot; is a bad question.  And for more than just the reasons the question you've quoted is considered bad for SO:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason that question doesn't fit on SO is because there is no single right answer. In other words, it is a &quot;list question.&quot;  It will solicit multiple, equally-correct answers. It will therefore be impossible for a single correct answer to be accepted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More unique to a movie reviewers question, the answers are &lt;em&gt;completely subjective&lt;/em&gt;.  Some reviewers I read because they like the same movies I like.  Other reviewers I read because they hate the movies I like, so I always do the opposite of what they suggest.  Other movie reviewers are all over the board.  It is impossible to recommend a reviewer in an objective way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR;&lt;/strong&gt; It should be off-topic to ask for &quot;reviewer recommendations&quot; because of the list nature, and subjective nature of the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, having said that, it may be reasonable to ask some questions about reviews or reviewers that are a good fit for an SE site.  But they won't be subjective or list questions.  If I can think of such an example question, I will add it here.... but I can't think of one at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="22" LastEditDate="2011-12-03T01:24:57.800" LastActivityDate="2011-12-03T01:24:57.800" CommentCount="8" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="68" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-03T02:10:05.750" Score="3" ViewCount="47" Body="&lt;p&gt;I figured I would push this question out there to get the ball rolling (Early bird gets the worm no?). I think extended discussion of promotion should be in the chatroom &lt;a href=&quot;http://chat.stackexchange.com/rooms/1888/movies&quot;&gt;http://chat.stackexchange.com/rooms/1888/movies&lt;/a&gt;, it is alot easier than refreshing this meta page and then come here when we have definite answers to this question. What do you think?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Who do we ask? What sites should we email?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do think though that when we do this, we should do it in one big media blitz. One intense first day where we get as much as media as once on one day (whenever public beta opens) then let organic traffic take care of the rest after that for a while.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-03T02:10:05.750" Title="How do we promote our site (when it goes public beta)?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;7-essential&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="69" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="63" CreationDate="2011-12-03T04:33:08.223" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Discussing the acting or writing elements that made the movie &lt;em&gt;work&lt;/em&gt; isn't necessarily &quot;trivia.&quot; It's directly related to the appreciation of the film. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don't pick apart the dictionary definition of &quot;trivia&quot; for your acid test (sorry @Flimzy). &lt;em&gt;Trivia&lt;/em&gt; is those little bits of completely expendable knowledge you keep in your head that nobody needs to know. &lt;em&gt;&quot;Did Marilyn Monroe have six toes?&quot;&lt;/em&gt; Who cares; It has absolutely &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt; to do with the appreciation of the actress or her movies. It's idle curiosity; That's all. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When trying to measure triviality, asking yourself how many of the following words apply: minutiae, trite, dispensable, superfluous, vacuous &amp;mdash; or just ask yourself: &quot;Does this question help my understanding or appreciation for the film (beyond idle curiosity)?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This site is for &quot;film aficionados&quot; &amp;mdash; or at least it should be &amp;mdash; and I'm hoping this site is interested in the deeper aspects of film appreciation. Perhaps the word I am looking for is &quot;fervent&quot;; A deeper appreciation for the finer points of a subject rather than the banal chit-chat you might entertain friends with around the water cooler. But it's been done thousands of time on every other site on the subject. I think you can do better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastActivityDate="2011-12-03T04:33:08.223" CommentCount="4" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="70" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="71" CreationDate="2011-12-04T03:44:15.687" Score="5" ViewCount="109" Body="&lt;p&gt;Now I am going to say it up front, I am by no means someone one who academically nor professionally studies film so it would be good if someone who has actually participated in Film Studies weigh in on this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First I would like to say that the following questions are indeed subjective&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/48/what-is-the-main-theme-in-dark-knight&quot;&gt;What is the main theme of The Dark Knight?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/55/captain-miller-thought-process-in-private-ryan-school-teacher-scene&quot;&gt;Captain Miller&amp;#39;s thought process in Private Ryan &amp;quot;School Teacher&amp;quot; scene?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/176/is-the-opening-break-up-scene-in-the-social-network-intended-to-be-humorous&quot;&gt;Is the opening break-up scene in The Social Network intended to be humorous?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/137/how-do-the-differences-appear-between-the-four-replicants-and-blade-runner&quot;&gt;How do the differences between the replicants and Deckard evolve in Blade Runner?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/177/what-fills-the-void-left-by-the-lack-of-character-development-in-inception&quot;&gt;What fills the void left by the lack of character development in Inception?&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now the reason I decided to place these questions is to push towards analysis of the film though subjective, it is still analysis of the film in the eyes of the viewer. Let's look at the top voted questions currently (I am in no way attacking these questions but using them as examples),&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/5/is-there-a-definitive-explanation-to-the-ending-of-inception&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/5/is-there-a-definitive-explanation-to-the-ending-of-inception&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/13/in-shutter-island-is-there-any-definitive-evidence-that-teddy-was-or-was-not-cr&quot;&gt;Is there any definitive evidence that Teddy was or was not crazy?&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As seen in the Inception answer we have two views. One that Nolan wanted to give. And one that the viewer as arrived at via observations of the film. One could say the ring reasoning is just a coincidence, though it is very convincing. What am I getting at? There is an opinion in there different from what Nolan originally intended and it &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; give us a deeper appreciation of the film.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is actually the same thought process for Shutter Island, (interestingly the same actor). The point of Shutter Island was to again lead the audience in limbo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So do these questions which you actually might end up seeing in your regular film critic review , which are subjective, be left off this site? And if they are, what are we really left with?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identify items (music,objects,names,rooms,origins of items,movie titles)  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Definition of movie/camera terms&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Director explanations for why the plot/adaptations turned out a certain way  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am open to not having subjective questions but at the same time it seems to this closes the scope a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like to compare this to lit.stackexchange.com but I don't think it works. Works in books are descriptive, the writer uses words and phrases to ensure the reader gets the proper emotions and reasoning. This can be seen when many readers don't like how a film adaptation turns out. Because it is a certain view of how the book should be seen. (Hey this is my opinion, this could all be wrong)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyone care to me give me a little wisdom on subjectivity and film criticism and why it would not be a good for this site?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.220" LastActivityDate="2011-12-04T07:29:21.587" Title="Subjectivity and Film Study : How to deal with it?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="71" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="70" CreationDate="2011-12-04T07:14:09.877" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;Not everyone is intimately familiar with the history of Stack Exchange, so I have to throw in the canonical response to &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Is subject [X] too subjective for a Stack Exchange site.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; The following should be virtually &lt;em&gt;required&lt;/em&gt; reading for this site —&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good Subjective, Bad Subjective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It outlines how to develop inherently &lt;em&gt;subjective&lt;/em&gt; subjects into a Q&amp;amp;A that is constructive, informative and helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;On &amp;quot;Film Study&amp;quot;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has a nice, academic ring to it. But I'm still a bit leery if such a mainstream subject can keep that academic bent we need to build truly great Q&amp;amp;A. I'm not talking about university-level studies. I'm talking about questions that would be asked by those with an avid appreciation for the subject.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest challenges of this site is — believe it or not — the &lt;em&gt;VAST&lt;/em&gt; scope of its audience. Everybody has something to say about movies they've seen. That's why there's are 10's of thousands of sites on the subject. &lt;strong&gt;But we don't &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; those questions that have been asked hundreds of times on every other site on the subject!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's the problem. You have a scope where virtually anyone is well-equipped to throw in their random opinion on a movie they've seen. But what's even worse is the range of the &lt;em&gt;questions&lt;/em&gt; that can be asked about those movies. &lt;em&gt;Huh?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;Movie appreciation&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt; has such a broad &lt;em&gt;range&lt;/em&gt; of &amp;quot;expertise.&amp;quot; &lt;em&gt;Anyone&lt;/em&gt; can ask a question about a movie. Moreso, everybody &lt;em&gt;wants&lt;/em&gt; to talk about the latest flick or a nostalgic pop classic. But I'm hoping this site can rise above the water cooler chit-chat and keep to the &lt;em&gt;finer&lt;/em&gt; points of the subject; the connoisseurs — those who understand the finer details, techniques, and  principles of cinema and is competent to act as a critical judge and teacher; One who enjoys with discrimination and appreciation of subtleties of this whole subject.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If we can avoid falling into the predictable patterns of random discussion and trivia swapping that turn a site from a learning experience into a glorified game show, this will be a great site. But I'm leery that a site with such a broad pop-culture appeal can muster up the tough love to actively, aggressively, and jealously guard it form becoming very pedestrian.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2020-06-04T15:14:02.303" LastActivityDate="2011-12-04T07:29:21.587" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="72" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-12-04T22:37:44.983" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;After I asked one for myself, I will add my thoughts about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First: It is very useful for the asker, if he gets a good answer. You have this personal demon, he shows you again and again this image of a movie you have seen years ago, but you can't remember more. Was it good or bad? No idea. For some reason this image has burnt into your mind. Asking about identification here can help: you can rewatch the movie and see if it was bad or good and why it is on your mind. If it was bad, you can forget about it afterwards in peace. If it was good, you remember now a good movie, you would otherwise would have forgot about. Very useful for the asker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But is it useful for someone else? Others will nearly never have the same images that have burnt into their minds. So even when they try to remember the same movie, they will have to ask for themself. Answers for identify-questions aren't good recommendations either. The movies discussed here may be horrible. Do you have any reason to look at any of &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/identify-this-movie&quot;&gt;these questions&lt;/a&gt;, except the ones you asked yourself? Can you upvote an answer - you don't really know if it is the movie the OP wanted to know about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems these questions are of no lasting value. Is it enough, that it helped the OP very much? Possibly it is. I'm not sure about that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will try out if my concerns are consensus in the community. So I will vote to close all identify-questions that have an accepted answer (are solved). As my argumentation shows, I think these will be no longer of use for anyone else, the OP got an answer if he accepted one. I'm open to discussion if they should be banned generally, but for now I will try to close the ones that are answered. Sorry if that seems to be forcing a decision, but as &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/a/86/66&quot;&gt;this answer&lt;/a&gt; suggests, that's the way the policy is formed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.943" LastActivityDate="2011-12-07T12:04:17.167" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="73" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="74" CreationDate="2011-12-04T23:06:47.180" Score="6" ViewCount="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/205/49&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt;, which is a kind of plot-hole question, if you want. The question, being about &quot;Hunt for Red October&quot;, has the tags &lt;code&gt;submarine&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;cold-war&lt;/code&gt; (which the movie's story is about in general), though it is not really a question about the movie's overall story, one of those topics or movies about those topics in general (it is somehow related to submarine technology, but this is no Q&amp;amp;A site about applied nuclear physics, and it's more of a plot-hole question really). So I think those tags are not really fitting here and such behaviour could lead to a tag explosion of the question (though I know it's limited to 5, but even worse, which to pick from a large variety) or maybe the site?.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So is this appropriate for this question? Is it only appropriate if the question really has a connection to these topics? Or is it not really fitting at all to intoduce such &quot;content theme&quot; tags, as there are movies about everything but often the question is not about space travels in general, but about &quot;Star Wars&quot; or maybe Science Fiction in general (genre tags are a good idea, of course)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="49" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.943" LastActivityDate="2011-12-09T00:53:34.790" Title="General theme tags" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="74" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="73" CreationDate="2011-12-05T01:25:22.457" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;The submarine and cold-war tags make no sense. I have removed them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please keep it limited to movie name and genre for now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additional tags include, analysis, movie-identification, ending.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T01:25:22.457" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="75" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-12-05T03:48:50.990" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;This site is going to have &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/identify-this-movie&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;identify-this-movie&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;identify-this-movie&lt;/a&gt; questions. It's almost a rite of passage&amp;hellip; &lt;strong&gt;and then you'll regret it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The people who &lt;em&gt;ask&lt;/em&gt; the questions will love them. They're really simple to ask; they're like crossword puzzles: &lt;em&gt;&quot;I'm thinking of a word; 7-letters; beginning with the letter 'N'.&quot;&lt;/em&gt; It's like playing a gameshow. It will be a small minority users who get sick and tired of seeing them day after day &amp;mdash; unfortunately, they'll be the most avid users on this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can already see from the responses here that you'll embrace these questions as &lt;em&gt;'mostly harmless'.&lt;/em&gt; The problem is they are easy to ask, but they ultimately help exactly &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt; person, and then they're useless. It gets tiresome, and drives away avid users who drive this site.  They will continue to pervade the question space. &lt;strong&gt;And then they wear down a community.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gaming.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/2674/do-we-still-like-identify-this-game-questions&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do we still like 'Identify This Game' questions?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first &lt;em&gt;buzz&lt;/em&gt; I heard about this site &amp;mdash; before I even got a chance to see how it was going for myself &amp;mdash; was &lt;em&gt;(I'm paraphrasing&amp;hellip;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;They're already starting with the identify-this-{thing}&quot;&lt;/em&gt; questions &amp;hellip; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;Won't they ever learn?&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's really hard to articulate as to &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; these questions are not good for this site; but suffice it to say that, once they permeate the front page, a few users will work long and hard to try and get rid of them. But the masses will keep them coming&amp;hellip; inexorably. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the earliest formative days of this site, the [identify-this-movie] tag is already approaching 10% of the questions. In a not-too-distant future, most of those questions  will be asked by hit-and-run users who will never return to this site. And you'll get bored having to tease out a decent question and provide answers to a post that will not add one lick of value or interest to this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="69" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:43:44.900" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T14:09:40.653" CommentCount="6" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="76" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="78" CreationDate="2011-12-05T04:32:42.513" Score="2" ViewCount="108" Body="&lt;p&gt;I deleted my original &quot;Push more questions&quot; drive, just to jump the gun but users replied with &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;quality is needed not quantity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where are all these high quality questions for the last two days?!??&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Total questions: 76&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Total users: 163&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There were only&lt;br&gt;&#xA;3 questions asked today.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;2 questions asked yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Only 40 users asked questions out of 163 available &lt;em&gt;out of&lt;/em&gt; the 216 users committed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the Area51 FAQ&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Commit! When a proposal enters the &quot;Commitment&quot; phase, &lt;strong&gt;we will present a petition for the site's creation. Interested users are asked to digitally &quot;sign&quot; the proposal with their full name to help assure that site will have an active community in those critical early days.&lt;/strong&gt; While your full name is never shown, you may add an optional comment which is displayed alongside your username in the list of committers. To ensure that commitment is taken seriously, you may only commit to three sites at any one time. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are we taking commitment seriously? Or should we just close this site?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T10:10:24.457" Title="Why aren't users asking questions?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="5" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="77" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="76" CreationDate="2011-12-05T06:16:28.907" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Taking this site seriously means asking questions when the need arises, not just to create activity. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the number of questions is good for the subject. What we need is more users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T06:16:28.907" CommentCount="8" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="78" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="76" CreationDate="2011-12-05T10:10:24.457" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think most commited users asked their questions spared for this beta on the first days. Now we some drought on new questions as it is hard to come up with new. I think new users have fresh questions, so as the beta goes public this number will go up again. I think the private beta is more for defining the scope of the questions that should be asked. But only three questions a day don't define a scope. So we should come up with some more I think.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T10:10:24.457" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="79" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2011-12-05T18:34:35.193" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;identify-this&lt;/code&gt; questions are unique in that nearly everyone will have 1-3 things they need identified during their time on the site. When looking at statistics we need to keep this in mind. The large number of questions is in part because the tag is applicable to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With that said, I agree with Robert Cartaino that they wear down the community, however for somewhat different reasons. It's not the tag, it's the users. The ones who don't want to help the community, but still ask identify-this questions. I feel like if the tag isn't banned, then it needs to be a rep-based privilege.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2011-12-05T18:34:35.193" CommentCount="4" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="80" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="81" CreationDate="2011-12-05T19:39:01.907" Score="7" ViewCount="156" Body="&lt;p&gt;It seems odd to me to see the spoiler markup on a question about a movie from 1980.  i.e: &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/226/scene-during-the-ending-of-the-shining&quot;&gt;What does the scene during the ending represent?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should there be an age-limit on spoilers?  One would think given a reasonable amount of time since a movie's release one would have figured out how to avoid information about it and/or have watched it already.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="32" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.587" LastActivityDate="2014-04-23T09:12:27.697" Title="Statute of Limitations on Spoilers?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;spoilers&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="81" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="80" CreationDate="2011-12-05T20:41:07.003" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;See: &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/114876/policy-for-spoilers-on-fiction-or-literature-sites&quot;&gt;Policy for spoilers on fiction or literature sites?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For extended discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But the gist of it; there is no policy network wide. If most of your question uses the spoiler markup don't use it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I already removed the spoiler markup for that question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a movie came out 10 years ago, I really would like to think you were spoiled in some way or another between now and then. You really are not going to watch the movie the day or even the week after you saw the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are even two tags there&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ending  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;name of movie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This should hint to someone who doesn't want to be spoiled &lt;em&gt;not to click on the question&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example this is a problem in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/325Fo.png&quot; alt=&quot;Words are where?&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-20T10:29:51.513" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T01:36:07.337" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="82" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="83" CreationDate="2011-12-06T00:32:12.913" Score="23" ViewCount="533" Body="&lt;p&gt;As others have recently commented on the 'statute of limitations' on spoilers, I am wondering whether we are overusing the spoiler markup period.  It strikes me that the spoiler markup is somewhat irritating as you are reading and/or responding to a question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems to me, as long as the subject is not a spoiler of a recent movie, then everything else is fair game - i.e. no need for spoiler markup in questions or answers at all.  If you read a question about a movie that you have not yet seen - then it is your fault.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do people think?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastEditorUserId="49" LastEditDate="2015-12-28T15:51:24.003" LastActivityDate="2015-12-28T15:51:24.003" Title="Are we overusing the spoiler markup?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;spoilers&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="83" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="82" CreationDate="2011-12-06T01:46:39.890" Score="17" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some people are overusing the spoiler markup. I don't know how else to say it ... it gets in the way of reading the question and answers. It is irritating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unsigned's edit to my question: &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/249/why-are-vincents-and-spikes-souls-similar&quot;&gt;Why are Vincent&amp;#39;s and Spike&amp;#39;s souls similar?&lt;/a&gt; is a good restricted use of spoiler markup in my opinion. If the spoiler markup uses more that 70% of the question/answer body, &lt;em&gt;don't use it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am going to quote &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/114876/policy-for-spoilers-on-fiction-or-literature-sites/114923#114923&quot;&gt;badp's answer&lt;/a&gt; who requested the use of spoiler markup,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Your question must make sense without spoiler protected paragraphs    &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Your answer must make sense without spoiler protected paragraphs   &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Your title must be easy to Google for. If that means spoilery, so be it&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.943" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T01:46:39.890" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="84" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="203" CreationDate="2011-12-06T05:56:23.690" Score="6" ViewCount="83" Body="&lt;p&gt;The climax in some movies are interpreted differently by different people. When a question related to the ending of movies like &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/226/scene-during-the-ending-of-the-shining&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; is asked. What are the important points to be considered when accepting an answer. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question also applies for analysis of movies, &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/60/what-has-the-greatest-chance-of-being-in-marcellus-wallaces-briefcase-in-pulp-f&quot;&gt;example here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="96" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.587" LastActivityDate="2012-01-05T21:43:38.663" Title="Awarding accept answer for endings and analysis" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;accepted-answer&gt;&lt;analysis&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="85" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-06T12:01:03.003" Score="4" ViewCount="38" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are some questions here on meta, that are asked to find a proper policy. How are they decided.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some examples:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/q/32/66&quot;&gt;Identify This Movie Questions?&lt;/a&gt;: Should I vote to close them or encourage them?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/q/70/66&quot;&gt;Subjectivity and Film Study : How to deal with it?&lt;/a&gt;: Same here, are we closing such questions?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/q/65/66&quot;&gt;Questions about reviews and reviewers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/q/15/66&quot;&gt;Should we cover TV Series here?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/q/43/66&quot;&gt;What's trivia and where do we draw the line?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, is there a way to form from this questions a policy? Or should I decide myself after reading the different points (and made one myself)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:49:37.130" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T14:48:19.543" Title="How will meta-discussion be decided?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="86" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="85" CreationDate="2011-12-06T14:48:19.543" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I believe that a successful stack-exchange site becomes (largely) self regulating as people gain privileges including the ability to close questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is the responsibility of the people that have these privileges to conform to the policy that is worked out through the meta-discussion, which of course may change with time as the site grows, and problems arise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is the safety net of the stack-exchange assigned moderators.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only thing I am not aware of are how to change the FAQ.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T14:48:19.543" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="87" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="65" CreationDate="2011-12-06T16:50:03.340" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think that a limited number of 'list' questions are acceptable in a SE site.  There are a number in Stackoverflow, which have not been deleted because they serve a purpose.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I agree that they are not to be encouraged, hence the 'is not considered a good, on-topic question' part of the description applied to these questions on Stackoverflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The moderators of Stackoverflow have clearly allowed these specific questions to exist, but do not want them to become a model for future question asking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, on the specifics of a Review recommendations page, I think that one question of this sort should be allowed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T16:50:03.340" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="88" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="65" CreationDate="2011-12-06T16:59:45.820" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;As I pointed out in the comment to &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/q/265/66&quot;&gt;Alternative to IMDB to read movie reviews and check ratings&lt;/a&gt; I'm not completely against it. But the focus should be narrow. Because if the question is so unfocused like the example I gave or the example @iandotkelly gave (most influential book for programmers) the answers will hold a wide range of links. To someone else finding this over google it is of not too much use, because he effectively have to check all links to find something matching his needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I think these questions could be all right, if the focus is much more narrow. In the case of the review-site-question it would help, if the question states why IMDB is not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.587" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T16:59:45.820" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="89" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="84" CreationDate="2011-12-06T17:24:31.057" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;First of all: I get more and more the impression, that accept is no good feature for SE-sites, in fact it may even be harmful. As I started on Stackoverflow, it seemed reasonable. I have a problem, someone have a solution, I accept this answer. But it often happens, that days later someone posts a better answer. I may miss it, because I'm sometimes inactive for weeks. So the not so good answer is accepted, the better is not, although it gets more votes with the time. Accepts are actually harmful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I start to think, that no question exists, that has only one correct answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyways, the system is like it is, and accepts give much reputation (even ignoring the cap) and your accept-rate is part of the user-card. So it is no option to avoid accepts altogether. So what can we do with question, there multiple good answers can be given.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, if actually after some time only one good answer exists, I give it the accept. If multiple exists, I may choose one, mostly the one giving the best references. I sometimes comment to point out other answers, that I also considered for the accept.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T17:24:31.057" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="90" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="94" CreationDate="2011-12-06T19:53:10.913" Score="5" ViewCount="49" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just noticed a typo in the tag &lt;code&gt;cowboy-behop&lt;/code&gt; - it should be &lt;code&gt;cowboy-bebop&lt;/code&gt;. I didn't find any link to signal that kind of errors though. Rare as they are, maybe it's not really needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastEditorUserId="49" LastEditDate="2015-09-22T12:04:04.277" LastActivityDate="2015-09-22T12:04:04.277" Title="How do we signal a typo in a tag?" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="91" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="80" CreationDate="2011-12-06T19:54:21.570" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I totally disagree. Just because a movie came out in 1980 and I haven't seen it in 2011 does NOT mean that I'll either never see the movie or have already heard/seen spoilers at some point already. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I took half a dozen film classes in college, and many of the movies I watched there I had never heard about until I took that class. One of them was &lt;em&gt;Metropolis&lt;/em&gt; - it came out in 1927, but how many people in the world have actually seen it? There are additional movies that professors recommended we watch if we had the time or inclination that are on my To Watch list but I haven't been able to hunt down or make time for in the past few years. That doesn't mean I never want to watch them and that I &lt;em&gt;won't&lt;/em&gt; watch them. It means I have a Very Long List, and Netflix only has so many of them available on Instant Watch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, having said that, I'm not going to insist that there be spoiler markup on every question that talks about the ending of a movie. As Alonzo mentioned, there are (at least &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be) other clues that allow people to avoid questions they don't want to be - tags are useful for that. As has been stated in other discussions elsewhere on the network, spoiler markup is a courtesy thing. I &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; think if someone uses spoiler markup, no one should go back to edit it out, even if you personally think that there's no reason for it. If the OP felt like being polite, let them be polite.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A separate issue is the one of the entire body of a post being spoiler markup. But that's a different conversation, &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.meta.stackexchange.com/questions/82/are-we-overusing-the-spoiler-markup&quot;&gt;taking place on a different meta thread&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-16T15:49:37.243" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T19:54:21.570" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="92" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="82" CreationDate="2011-12-06T20:01:35.630" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I pretty much agree with Alonzo's answer, but I wanted to suggest a TL;DR version of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/114876/policy-for-spoilers-on-fiction-or-literature-sites/114923#114923&quot;&gt;answer Alonzo quoted&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/a/91695/166017&quot;&gt;This one is also from badp&lt;/a&gt;, but it's a little older and provides a side-by-side comparison of good spoiler markup v. bad spoiler mark-up. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;People won't answer questions if we make it obnoxious to find out what is actually being asked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-03-20T10:29:51.513" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T20:01:35.630" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="94" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="90" CreationDate="2011-12-06T22:01:17.233" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is no way to fix a typo in a tag (i.e change tag &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/stak&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;stak&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;stak&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/stack&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged &amp;#39;stack&amp;#39;&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;stack&lt;/a&gt;). These are now two different tags.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Suggest an edit to all questions incorrectly tagged. For a large set do as you had did and post it on this meta. Those with 500 reputation and more should be able to review them in &lt;a href=&quot;https://movies.stackexchange.com/review/suggested-edits&quot;&gt;https://movies.stackexchange.com/review/suggested-edits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since there is currently only one, it would be best to signal the original poster of the question to edit. It will most likely be faster than waiting for someone to see the suggestion in /review.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I removed my typo and the incorrect tag should hopefully be out of system &lt;a href=&quot;https://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/48417/should-we-zap-the-low-occurrence-tags/48418#48418&quot;&gt;in about a day&lt;/a&gt; as long as no one uses it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sorry about that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastEditorUserId="1" LastEditDate="2017-04-13T12:54:01.943" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T22:01:17.233" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="95" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="123" CreationDate="2011-12-06T22:31:09.123" Score="4" ViewCount="42" Body="&lt;p&gt;When you try to flag a post as off-topic, the only option you get is to suggest to migrate is to meta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can I suggest we start to have some more options here, for example&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;literature.stackexchange.com&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;scifi.stackexchange.com&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are suggested as it is probably going to be common for people to ask about plot points that might be better addressed in the story the movie was adapted from.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I ask this as it seems more rude to suggest 'this is off topic' whereas 'this would be better on xx' seems a lot more constructive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastEditorUserId="49" LastEditDate="2015-09-23T18:28:52.383" LastActivityDate="2015-09-23T18:28:52.383" Title="Request for better 'belongs on' suggestions for flagging as off topic" Tags="&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;status-deferred&gt;&lt;migration&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="96" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="95" CreationDate="2011-12-06T22:46:50.393" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Migrations in private beta are not possible as no one knows whether the site will survive or not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the site passes into public beta I am sure these options will be available (the developers would have already made the suitable choice to put them in the correct sites for migration when public beta time is ready)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point for now is to show what belongs and does not belong in scope and to edit the FAQ scope as such.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T22:46:50.393" CommentCount="3" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="97" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="90" CreationDate="2011-12-06T22:48:22.647" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you don't have access to retag or edit the question, you can always flag the question for moderator attention, and describe the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2011-12-06T22:48:22.647" CommentCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="98" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2011-12-07T13:20:35.353" Score="7" ViewCount="61" Body="&lt;p&gt;Should shorts be in-topic? That includes for instance:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the three &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.blender.org/features-gallery/blender-open-projects/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;blender-movies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_jet%C3%A9e&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;La Jeteé&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;most of the work of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000122/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Charlie Chaplin&lt;/a&gt; before 1923&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If we want to exclude short-movies, where is the line? 30 Minutes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="68" LastEditDate="2011-12-07T22:55:21.650" LastActivityDate="2011-12-08T12:40:39.687" Title="Are short movies on-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="0" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
  <row Id="99" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="98" CreationDate="2011-12-07T14:10:46.663" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since they are not only movies by name, but usually also encompass all aspects of &quot;long&quot; movies, they should be perfectly Ok, I think.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="49" LastEditorUserId="49" LastEditDate="2011-12-08T12:40:39.687" LastActivityDate="2011-12-08T12:40:39.687" CommentCount="2" ContentLicense="CC BY-SA 3.0" />
</posts>
